<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AX SSG</title>
    <description>Demo site built with AX SSG - minimalist static site generator with modern design - by Axcora tech</description>
    <link>https://ax.axcora.com/</link>
    <item>
<title><![CDATA[Welcome to Axcora AX SSG: Static Site Generation Reinvented]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/welcome-to-axcora-ax-ssg.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-09-01</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The digital world is constantly evolving, and website developers are always searching for better ways to build and deploy fast, secure, and robust web experiences. Axcora AX SSG is an innovative static site generator designed around three goals: simplicity, speed, and developer happiness.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why Speed Matters: Supercharge Your Website with AX SSG]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/speed-matters.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-30</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Website speed isn&#39;t just a technical metric—it&#39;s a measure of user experience and business impact. Study after study shows that users are less likely to engage, convert, or return to slow websites. Google and other search engines now factor speed heavily into rankings, making fast-loading sites a top priority for SEO.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Static vs Dynamic Websites: Why Go Static in 2025?]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/static-vs-dynamic-websites.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-30</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The debate between static and dynamic websites is not new, but in recent years the advantages of static sites have become clearer than ever. Static sites, like those generated by Axcora AX SSG, pre-render every page at build time. This means that visitors receive perfectly optimized HTML files, resulting in lightning-fast load times.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Power of Minimalism: Clean Web Development with AX]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/the-power-of-minimalism.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-29</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In a world flooded with frameworks, plugins, and dependencies, minimalism offers a refreshing approach to web development. By stripping away excess complexity, you gain not only better performance but also maintainability and clarity in your codebase.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Getting Started with AX SSG The Essential Guide]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/getting-started-with-axcora-ssg.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-28</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Starting a new project with Axcora AX SSG is fast and intuitive. The first step is to install AX via the official CLI and initialize a project skeleton with the <code>ax init &lt;project&gt;</code> command. This creates a clean folder structure, including directories for your content, templates, assets, and site data.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Handlebars Templates: Unleash Your Creativity with AX SSG]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/handlebars-templates-for-web-creativity.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-17</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Templates are the heart of every website, defining how content is presented and how visitors experience your brand. Axcora AX SSG uses Handlebars as its template engine, offering a familiar and powerful way to create flexible page layouts.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Axcora AX SSG vs. Traditional Static Site Generators: Key Differences]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/ax-ssg-vs-traditional-generators.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-14</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>When choosing a static site generator for your project, it’s important to weigh the strengths of different solutions. Many established SSGs—such as Jekyll, Hugo, or Gatsby—offer robust feature sets, strong community support, and plugins for nearly every need. However, these frameworks often introduce complexity, large node_modules directories, and longer setup times.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Automate Your SEO: Sitemaps, RSS, and Robots with AX SSG]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/automate-your-seo-with-ax-ssg-by-axcora.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-11</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Search Engine Optimization (SEO) is essential for any public website, but configuring SEO tools and metadata can be a time-consuming task. With AX SSG by axcora team, you get advanced SEO automation out of the box, so you can focus more on your content and design.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open Source and Community-Driven: The Future of AX Cora SSG]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/open-source-and-community-driven.html</link>
<pubDate>2025-08-10</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#39;s technology landscape, open-source software is more important than ever. It fosters collaboration, rapid innovation, and a sense of shared ownership within developer and designer communities. Axcora AX SSG proudly embraces this philosophy with an open-source core and accessible development model.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Simple Content Management with Markdown and AX SSG]]></title>
<link>https://ax.axcora.com/blog/simple-content-management-with-markdown.html</link>
<pubDate>2023-08-16</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Content should be easy to create, edit, and maintain—without complex databases or clunky CMS systems. Axcora AX SSG uses Markdown files as its core content format, marrying powerful features with a user-friendly writing experience.</p>
]]></description>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>